上菜 鸡胸肉
Pick up... chicken breasts.
我做了你爱的那样 内含"硬骨"
The way I know you want it, with the bone in.
我们真应该开个工作场合性骚扰研讨会
We really should hold a seminar about sexual harassment in the workplace.
为什么 他早是骚扰界一霸了
Why? He's already so good at it.
说真的 如果是我们
I'm serious. How'd he like it
每次点菜都骚扰他 他会做何感想
if we did that to him every time we ordered?
试试便知
Well, let's find out.
点菜
Ordering.
一份熏牛肉
One pastrami.
可以帮我个忙吗 小美妞
Can you do me a favor, doll-face?
把牛肉弄得又大又粗 一嘴含不住塞不下
Make it so big and thick, you can't get your mouth around it.
能为我做到吗 小甜心
Can you do that for me, sweetheart?
再来两份薄饼肉丸汤
Yes, and two matzo ball soups,
不放"肉丸"
hold the balls.
不 "肉丸"放我手里就好
Wait, I'll hold the balls,
你就美美的乖乖坐着享受吧
you just sit there and look pretty.
再一份白液...
And a cream of...
不行了 说得我都吐了
nope, can't. Just grossed myself out.
什么时候才要开始说黄段子啊
When is it going to get dirty?
麦克斯 出来[出柜]吧
Max, come out.
如果我要出柜 肯定不是因为你
If I came out, it would not be for you,
而是为了那个火辣的龙纹身女孩
it's be for that hot Dragon Tattoo girl.
各位董事会成员 欢迎出席首届
Welcome, board members, to the very first
麦克斯自制小蛋糕店的财务评估会议
financial assessment meeting of Max's homemade cupcakes.
我是听说有起司拼盘才来的
I was told there would be a cheese plate.
开业五个月
After five months in business,
我们的收益为725元
we're showing a profit of $725.
老实说 我感到有点失望
I have to say, I'm a little disappointed.
真的吗 有这样的收益
Really? 'Cause, dude, we have so far exceeded
比我预期中五个月后的下场好多了
where I thought we'd be in five months.
我们得想个办法赚点外快
Look, we have to find a way to make more money on the side
好增加开店基金
to put into the business.
或趁现在小有成就 赶紧金盆洗手
Or we could quit now, while we're a success.
你这什么话
What are you talking about?
未来只会每况愈下
It's only gonna get worse.
也可以蒸蒸日上啊 你干嘛这么悲观
Or it could get better. Why would you even say that?
这就是人生 人生只会每况愈下
Because it's life, and life gets worse, that's what it does.
如果"人生"有简历 那专长栏上肯定写着
On life's resume, under special skills it says,
"擅于使情况每况愈下"
"Good at making things worse."
为什么你总是往最坏的方面想呢
Do you always go to the worst-case scenario?
没错 我的简历就写着
Yup. On my resume it says,
"擅于往最坏的方面想"
"Good at going to the worst case scenario."
你能不能乐观一点
Do you think you could try to be more optimistic,
不要总往最坏的方面想呀
and not expect the worst all the time?
-谁啊 -要我乐观是吧
- Who's that? - More optimistic, right?
门的另一边 是你失去的亿万家财
On the other side of that door is all the money you lost,
我们欢喜搬回你的别墅
and then we move back into your townhouse,
换我在你的小缸缸里自慰到爽
and I masturbate in your tub for a change.
我就做过两次 谁让你当时不敲门
It was twice, and you could have knocked.
谁啊
Who is it?
纽约警察局 詹姆士探员
Detective James, NYPD.
等等 别开门 别开门
Wait, don't open it! Don't open it!
开吧 大麻周二抽完了 没事
Oh, smoked it tuesday. Open.
抱歉打扰了 女士们 你们住在这里吗
Sorry to bother you, miss. Do you live in this apartment?
我现在就坦白 警官大人
I'm gonna tell you right now, officer,
我们的名字不在租约上
our names aren't on the lease.
我们是无地可住的非法转租客
We're an illegal sublet with no place else to go.
求您了 高抬贵手啊
Please, mercy.
警官 抱歉 这是她第一次被检查
Sorry, officer, it's her first raid.
别紧张 不是房东叫我来的
Relax, the landlord didn't send me.
你们认识
What do you know about the tenant
住在楼上的房客吗
who lives in the apartment directly above you?
他叫卢
His name is Lou.
里欧
Leo?
索尔
Saul?
我猜得接近吗
Am I even close?
他名字叫 尼尔翰·沙多里[印度名]
His name's Nirham Chaduri.
哎哟 跟我猜的差了十万八千里啊
Oh, man, I wasn't even on the right continent.
那是尼尔翰·沙多里吗...
Is that Nirham Chaduri?
死了两周了 独居 死无人知
Been dead for two weeks. Lived alone, nobody knew.
他的脸有被猫吃掉吗
Cats eat his face?
麦克斯 想法不要这么阴暗好吗
Max, could you please not be so dark?
他的脸有被小喵喵吃掉吗
Kittens eat his face?
干嘛 我是想添加点正面元素嘛
What? I'm just trying to put a more positive spin on things.
你拿着那个去哪呢
Where are you going with that?
那可是带哈克狗图案的上好瓷碟啊
That's my good china with huckleberry hound on it.
这是我要给对门邻居的
I'm making a "Hello" Cupcake plate
问候小蛋糕盘
for our neighbors across the hall.
不行 不准你瞎搞
Oh, no, you're not.
不认识自己邻居 太不合理了
It's weird not to know your neighbors.
不认识自己老爸 才不合理呢
No, it's weird not to know your father,
不过等到四岁之后 你也就习惯不纠结了
but by the time you're four, you get over it and move on.
你这是在自掘坟墓
This is a mistake.
谁知道门后"潜伏"着什么怪人呢
Who knows what's lurking behind that door?
是呀 可怕着呢
Yes, something awful,
例如好人 那种会照看我们
like nice people, who might look out for us,
或是在走廊碰到会跟我们打招呼的好人
or say, "Hello", in the hallway when they see you.
我不管是什么牛鬼蛇神来应门
No matter what comes out of there,
我死也不会跟人在走廊里假客套
I will not be "hello-ing" It up in the hallway.
算你好运 赶紧回家
You got lucky. Get back in here.
请问哪位
Who is it, please?
卡洛琳 我是您的对门邻居
Caroline, your next-door neighbor.
你好
Hi.
没打扰到您吧
Uh, is this a bad time?
完全没有
Not at all.
-等一下 -你好
- One sec. - Hi.
我只是跟我室友麦克斯来打个招呼
I just wanted to introduce myself and my roommate, Max.
这俩小蛋糕是送您的
There, and give you these cupcakes.
你们人真好
That is so nice.
小小链子 不 小小心意而已
Well, it's the leash... least... least I can do.
好的 我有事先忙咯
Well, I gotta go.
如果我们养了狗 好歹知道谁能帮忙遛遛
Well, if we ever get a dog, we know who can walk it.
-你听 -我听到了
- Listen. - I know.
才几天而已
It's only been a few days,
楼上就搬进新住客了
and somebody's already moved in upstairs.
而且他们还在放音乐
And they are playing music!
这破音乐穿过屋顶 直达我的耳朵
Music is coming through the floor into my ears.
一切都怪你
I blame you for this.
你去敲对门的门的时候
When you knocked on that door across the hall,
你也开启了通往地狱的通道
you might have opened a portal to hell.
听到地狱的冥乐了吗
There, you hear the devil music?
人家是放比吉斯乐队吧
I think it's the Bee Gees.
那就是冥乐
Exactly.
还他妈大声走路
And walking!
大声走路和放音乐 我们得立刻制止这种行为
Walking and music, we have to stop this right now.
现在才10点 走路和放音乐没什么不可以
It's 10 o'clock, people are allowed to walk and play music.
你对住公寓毛都不懂
Your lack of apartment knowledge
真让老娘火大死了
is really starting to piss me off.
我们现在就得上去 给他个下马威
We have to show him right now not to screw us.
我需要白纸
I need paper.
你除了反应过度外 还想干嘛啊
What are you doing? I mean, besides over-reacting?
写恐吓信
Writing a threatening note.
如果一开始不处理 很快就会有
If we don't shut this down now, next thing you know,
路人跑来你家客厅 开奥斯卡颁奖晚会
someone's having an academy awards party in your living room.
你真想尝到这恶果吗
Is that what you want?
陌生人互相颁发迷你奥斯卡奖座
Strangers passing out mini Oscar statues
上面还写着"最佳玉米脆饼奖"
that say, "Best nachos?"
"我有把未注册的黑枪
"I have an unregistered gun
能从楼下一枪崩了你"
and can shoot you through the floor"?
你这样太火爆了吧 麦克斯
You're coming in really hot, Max.
这信不能给人家
We're not giving him this.
这会影响我们日后的邻里互动
It'll start a bad dynamic between us.
天啊 我好想念死去的印度无声无息男啊
God, how I miss the quiet, dead indian guy.
来吧 我们打完就跑
Okay, we're gonna hit and run.
你是说真跑啊
Oh, you mean "run," literally.
听好了
Shh, listen.
读信中
Reading the note,
惊讶中
freaking out...
音乐关掉 问题解决
Music off, problem solved.
厉害吧 感谢各位乡亲父老的支持
Respect! Never doubt, never doubt.
走向门中
Crossing the floor to the door,
关门中
Closing the door,
下楼中
Coming down the stairs,
我们该怎么办
What do we do?
搬家吗
Move?
他长什么样
What's he look like?
他用手指堵着猫眼呢
He's got his finger over the peephole.
很好 游戏开始 闪开
Okay, game on. Back up!
这是老娘的楼 老娘要夺回掌控权
This is my building, I've got to take it back.
麦克斯 这是现实生活
Max, this is life,
不是使命召唤3之现代大战
not Call of Duty: Modern warfare 3.
让开
Move.
敲个屁呀
What!
这封坏坏的信是什么意思
What is meaning of this horrible, horrible note?
你不是男人啊
Oh, you're not a man?
你这是哪门子的问题啊
What kind of question is this?
我看起来像个男人吗
Do I look like a man?
不像 不过你的走路声倒是十分爷们
No, but you clump around up there like a man.
麦克斯 别这样
Max, please.
这封坏坏的信是你写的吗
Did you write this horrible, horrible note?
没错
I did.
搬进新家的第一天
First day in my new home
我就收到这封这坏坏的...恐吓信
and I'm given this horrible, horrible note, with threats.
其实不算恐吓啦
Well, they're not actually threats.
"我要像杀猪那样宰了你"
"I will gut you like a hog."
我澄清一下 那信我只随便扫了一眼
To be clear, I only skimmed the note.
她行动太风风火火了
Everything was happening so fast.
显然我们一开始没给你留下好印象
Listen, we've obviously gotten off to a bad start.
您快请进
Please come in.
进来干嘛 你们还给我写了坏坏的...
Why would I want to come in with you horrible, horrible...
哇 小蛋糕天堂啊
ooh, cupcake land. Ooh.
是的 我们有个小蛋糕生意
Yes, we have a cupcake business.
虽然刚开始 不过生意还不错
We're just starting, but doing well.
麦克斯是蛋糕师 打声招呼吧
Max is the baker. Say hello, Max.
我认识黑帮的人哦
I know people in the mob.
她是麦克斯 我是卡洛琳 您叫...
That's Max, and I'm Caroline. You are?
苏菲·科臣斯基
Sophie Kuchenski.
没听错的话 是波兰口音吧
Is that a polish accent I'm detecting?
对
Yes.
我去过一次华沙[波兰首都] 爱死那里了
I visited Warsaw once, I love it.
我恨死那里了 老鼠和皮条客一堆
Oh, 'cause I hate it. Rats and pimps.
你怎么还不请我吃个小蛋糕
Why have you not yet offered me cupcake?
写了这种坏坏恐吓信 至少也得表示表示吧
It's the least thing you can do, after horrible, horrible note.
没问题 要巧克力的还是香草味的
Oh, sure. Chocolate or vanilla?
都要了
Yes.
干嘛一副苦瓜脸啊
Why such sourpuss?
不好意思啊
Sorry about that.
只是我们在附近餐馆上班 每天长时间工作
It's just, we work long hours at the neighborhood diner,
麦克斯还打两份工
and Max has another job as well,
回到家还得做这些小蛋糕
and then she comes home and she has to make the cupcakes.
太好吃了
Mmm. So good.
像她这种怨气冲天的人
How could someone so angry
怎么能做出如此美味的蛋糕呢
make something so sweet?
她也不总是这样啦
She's not always like this.
我这人就这样 问问你之前的住客就知道了
I'm usually like this, just ask the previous tenant.
等等 死人不能回答你
Oh, wait. You can't.
我觉得你们俩就像这俩小蛋糕
You know, you two girls are like these cupcakes.
一个又黑又重口 一个又白又松软
One is dark and heavy and one is light and fluffy.
我比较爱松软白妞
I prefer the fluffy one.
好吧 我想你懂我们的意思了
Well, I think we've made our point.
别放音乐 别大声走路
No music, no clumping,
不然我就一枪崩了你 慢走不送
I'll shoot you through the floor, thanks for stopping by.
真高兴我们关系好得都能乱开玩笑了
I'm so glad we can joke with each other already.
那封信 实在抱歉 我们可以重...
Sorry about the note, can we start ov...
你有香奈儿诱惑唇彩啊
you have the Chanel Allure lip gloss?
是啊
Yeah.
你也知道香奈儿啊
Mm, you know the Chanel?
何止知道 我爱死了 不过买不起了
Know? Love. I can't afford it any more.
来吧 拿一根走 我包里好多呢
Oh, take one. I got handfuls in my bag.
真的吗
Really?
你人真好
Oh, that's so nice.
喂
Hey.
喂 喂
Hey! Hey!
要我也帮你拴上狗链吗
Do I have to put you on a leash?
我们重新认识吧
Hey, we start again.
你拿一根香奈儿 我多拿几个小蛋糕走
You take a chanel, and I take more cupcakes to go.
当然 没问题
Oh, sure.
真乖
Yes.
我就知道 贱货骗了我们的蛋糕
I knew it. Bitch played us for cupcakes.
半夜三点 你居然还穿戴整齐
It's 3:00 A.M. Why are you dressed?
军人从不轻易脱下军装 得随时待命
Never took off my clothes, 'cause soldiers don't.
时刻做好敌袭的准备
We have to be ready when the enemy attacks.
好 你说得对 是我错了
Okay, you were right, I was wrong.
你拿扫把干嘛呢
Why do you have the broom?
我的手指子弹射完了啊
'Cause I ran out of finger bullets.
慢着 你会摔跤的
Wait, you're gonna fall.
真没想到我们还有扫把
I can't believe we have a broom.
一直以来我都是用杂志扫地
All this time I've been sweeping with an Us Weekly.
我早知会如此 只是当时懒得说你
I knew this would happen, but I didn't say anything,
因为你总说"麦克斯就爱往最坏的方面想"
'cause you were all, "Max is the worst-case scenario."
你看 我们一示弱 就是这下场
Well, we showed weakness and now, look.
我的意思是 你示弱了
And by "We," I mean "You."
接招吧 小蛋糕贼
Deal with this, cupcake thief!
再敲一次 大力点
Yeah, one more time, and hard.
现在我们的家都被她搞坏了 要战便战吧
Okay, now she broke our house. We're in a war.
她想跟姐斗 姐奉陪到底
She wants a piece of me, she's gonna get it.
我的高跟战鞋呢
Where are my heels?
她当姐是什么人啊
I mean, who did she think I am?
用管香奈儿就能收买的小笨妞吗
Someone she can just buy off with a tube of Chanel?
人家香奈儿一出 你的双腿
Well, your legs did kind of snap back
就开到脑后任人宰割了
over your head pretty quick when she offered it.
还以为是披萨"外送男"来了呢[常见黄片剧情]
I thought you were man with pizza.
你居然还有个阳台秋千
You have a porch swing in there.
你居然还抽着根电子香烟
You have an electric cigarette.
你们俩小妞找我做什么
What is it you two girls want?
我忘了
Uh, I forgot.
被屋里的一切和秋千晃傻眼了
Just so thrown by the swing and the everything.
你骗了我们
Oh, you're taking advantage of us
你无视约定 我行我素地放音乐
by still playing that music after we talked.
你们俩真是敬酒不吃吃罚酒啊
You two are harshing my marshmallow.
我明天只好打给我的房东好友了
So I'm gonna have to call my friend the landlord tomorrow
把你们写的坏坏信告诉他
and tell him about the horrible, horrible note.
我的天啊 她是个妓女
Oh, my God, she's a hooker.
我用了妓女的唇彩
I've been using a hooker's lip gloss.
她才不是妓女
She's not a hooker.
谢天谢地
Oh, good.
她这么老 肯定是老鸨啦
She's too old, she's a madame.
你用了人老珠黄的妓女的唇彩
You've been using an old hooker's lip gloss.
麦克斯 看我的嘴唇
Max, look, my lip.
有长东西吗 我感觉快长了
Is this something? I feel like I'm getting one.
我再说一次 疱疹不会在10小时内
For the last time, you cannot get a herpes breakout
爆发病徴的
in under ten hours.
有道理 现在是我一直往最坏的方面想
You're right, now I'm jumping to the worst-case scenario.
她的唇彩不见得会是疱疹病毒的繁殖地
Maybe her lip gloss wasn't a herpes breeding ground.
她也不见得是妓女
Maybe she's not a prostitute.
那些少女也不见得是被强制关在那里呢
Maybe those young girls weren't being held there against their will.
是啊 只是"刚好"有一些少女
Yeah, maybe she just has sleepovers
身着睡衣 荡着秋千留宿她家
with women on swings in the their nighties.
这种事 到处都有嘛
You know, like people do.
欢迎光临威廉斯堡餐厅
Welcome to Williamsburg diner.
您们多少人来派对呢
How many in your party?
这是哪门子的问题啊
What kind of question is this?
一个 我就是自己的派对
One, I am my own party.
我要坐卡座
I take booth.
哎哟喂呀 那靓妞是谁呢
Now, now, who is that over there?
我们楼上的新邻居
Our new upstairs neighbor.
厄尔 你觉得她看上去像是妓女吗
Earl, does she look like a prostitute to you?
我不喜欢以貌取人 以皮论书
Well, I don't like to judge a book by its cover,
可如果她真是本书
but if she was a book,
她就是其他书愿付钱搞的那种书
she'd be the kind that other books pay for sex.
苏菲来店里了 厄尔也觉得她是妓女
Sophie just came in, Earl thinks she's a hooker,
现在我嘴唇感觉好"一代名妓"啊
and now my lip is feeling very Courtney Love.
是我请她来吃饭的
I invited her here for a free meal,
我们得把关系搞好
we have to make this work out for us.
昨晚她都恐吓我们要打给房东"好友"了
Last night, she threatened to call her "friend," the landlord,
绝不能让这事发生
and that can never happen.
我们是非法转租客
We're illegal tenants,
楼上吵总比没楼住来得好
and I'd rather have a noisy roof over my head than no roof.
让我来跟她谈
Let me do the talking.
你心情太差 可能说错话惹到人家
You're too upset, and you might say something insulting.
说错什么呀 "你好 谢谢你的唇彩
Like what? "Hi, thanks for the lip gloss
多亏了你 我才有机会尴尬地告知
and the series of uncomfortable conversations
我未来爱人们 唇蜜送我的疾病"
with every lover I'll have for the rest of my life."
不用你告知啊
You don't need to tell them,
他们最终会发现的
they'll figure it out eventually.
感谢你特地过来一趟
Hi, thanks for coming in.
我喜欢你们的制服
I like the uniforms.
你波涛汹涌 紧身上衣秀美胸
You fill out the front nicely,
你一马平川 齐臀小裙秀美腿
and you with no boobs, short-short skirts.
聪明妞
Smart girls.
我们想请你吃顿晚餐
Uh, we just wanted to offer you a free dinner,
向你赔礼道歉
as our way of apologizing.
你准备好点餐了吗
So are you ready to order?
这是哪门子的问题啊
What kind of question is this?
你们看到这坏坏的菜单了吗
Did you see this horrible, horrible menu?
在这里我们都不能好好谈话
We can't have nice conversation here.
明天我带你们去好地方吃饭 我请客
Tomorrow I take you to nice place, my treat.
您不用这么客气啦
Oh, you don't have to do that.
不不 我也想向你们道歉
No, no, I, too, want to apologize.
你们昨晚走了之后
You know, after you two left the other night,
我的妞们也说我太凶了
some of my girls said that I was harsh on you.
你的妞们
Your girls?
是啊 她们都在我手下上班
Yes, all those girls work for me.
抱歉 我得去一下洗手间
Excuse me, I have to go to the ladies' room right now
检查一下我的嘴唇
and look at my lips.
谢谢你请我们吃饭
Thank you so much for inviting us.
这上等鱼子酱吃得还开心吗
Are you enjoying that beluga?
太开心了 谢谢你
Mmm, so much. Thank you.
我几百年没吃过鱼子酱了
I haven't had caviar in forever. Mmm.
腿再开得大一点啊
Legs over your head much?
苦瓜脸小妞 不喜欢吃鱼子酱吗
So, sourpuss, you don't like caviar?
不喜欢 我就吃吃廉价的芝士汉堡
No, I'm more of a cheeseburger kind of girl.
这店好忙啊
This place is busy.
这些服务员肯定赚翻了
The waiters must make a fortune.
一晚上能赚300到350块吧
Oh, yeah, 300, 350 a night.
你们俩小妞呢
What do you girls make?
生意好时 一晚上也才60到80块
60 to 80 on a good night.
就赚这么点钱 你们怎么可能
And how do you expect you will accomplish cupcake business
开成小蛋糕店啊
on money like this?
我们才刚开始嘛
Well, we're just starting out.
靠这微薄薪资 得到猴年马月了吧
Yes, but at this rate, it will take forever.
其实我也有个远大梦想
You know, I, too, have big dream.
我想在波兰的湖边盖间避暑别墅
I am building summer house by lake in Poland.
你们想看吗
You want to see?
你有照片吗
Oh, you have pictures?
不 我有房子
No, I have house.
这是我建筑师给的模板
This is model from the architect.
我去哪里都带着它 激励自己
And I take it everywhere I am, to remember where I'm going.
挺厉害啊
It's cool.
你们这样的好女孩 应该赚得更多
See, girls like you should be making more money.
你们考虑一下来我这里上班吧
Maybe you could consider coming to work for me.
苏菲
Sophie!
谢谢你昨天送来我家的妞儿
Thank you for sending girl to my apartment yesterday.
她活干得好吗
Oh, did she do the job?
她干活无人能及啊
Oh, like no one ever before.
尽心尽力趴在地上 从下面来 再翻过来
Down on all fours, under, over,
再接着从下面来
under again. Oh!
我的妞们会干到让你满意为止
Well, my girls don't leave until you're satisfied.
要不让她一周来两次吧
Maybe she can come two times a week.
你想她什么时候来[高潮]都行啊
She can come whenever you want her to come.
她们俩也是你的妞吗
Are these two of your girls?
我们刚刚还正在谈呢
Well, we were just discussing that.
这位小妞感觉承受力很强哦
Well, this one here looks like she can take a lot.
"感谢"夸奖啊
Uh, thanks?
我朋友雅尼在吧台等我呢
My friend Yanni is at the bar.
他离婚后很需要你的服务呢
Since his divorce, he's in great need of your service.
-请[波兰语] -好的
- Prosze. - Oh, yes.
我离开一下 别碰我的小屋哦
Uh, excuse me, and, um, don't touch my house.
真不敢相信她真打算
I can't believe she would actually consider
邀请我们去做妓
asking us to be prostitutes.
就是啊
I know.
邀请我 合情合理
I mean, me, I get,
邀请你 纯属搞笑
but you, I don't see it.
你也听到他说了 我看起来"承受"力很强
You heard the guy, I look like I could "take a lot."
麦克斯 别闹了
Max, it's not funny.
我有可能因为那香奈儿唇彩而染性病
Isn't it bad enough I may have gotten herpes
还不够糟吗
from her chanel gloss?
我们当然不会去卖啦
Of course we're not gonna do it,
但拜托 你天生就不适合当妓女
but come on, you'd be a terrible hooker.
多谢 我当然不适合当妓女
Thank you, I would be a terrible hooker.
因为我有心 有灵魂 还有梦想
I have a heart, and soul, and dreams,
想坠入爱河 然后相夫教子
and want to fall in love and have a family.
就承认吧 你床技太差
Oh, just say it, you're bad in bed.
我们还是走人吧
Let's get out of here.
拜托 她当我是什么啊
I mean, really, who does she think I am?
为了追求更好的物质而出卖自己的人吗
Someone who would just sell myself to have nice things?
我再吃最后两口 然后立马走人
Let me just suck down a little more of this, and we're off.
我们现在走人
If we walk out of here now,
差不多就能直接走去流浪汉之家了
we can just keep walking to the homeless shelter.
宁愿当流浪汉 也不去做妓
Well, I'd rather be homeless than a hooker.
她来了 坐下
Here she comes. Sit down!
谢谢她 再委婉拒绝
Let's thank her and politely decline.
好啦 再接着讨论刚才的事
Okay, back to what we were discussing.
谢谢你
Uh, thanks.
感谢你的提议 不过还是算了吧
We appreciate the offer, but we are going to pass.
难道你们不想实现梦想吗
So you don't want to accomplish your dream?
这两件事不见得一定有关联吧
Well, uh, I'm not exactly sure those two things line up,
还是谢谢你了
but thanks.
我还以为你们是聪明妞呢
I thought you were smart girls.
我们是聪明妞
We are smart girls,
聪明妞才不会为了实现梦想
and smart girls don't have to sell their bodies
而出卖肉体呢
to accomplish their goals.
那么做也没有任何错啦
Not that there's anything wrong with that.
对你行得通 但对我们...
It works for you, but us?
她床技太差 我又是个苦瓜脸
Well, she's bad in bed and I have a sourpuss.
哪有男人想花钱搞我们啊
What guy wants to pay for that?
你们以为我是妓女吗
You think I am prostitute?
才不是 穿着睡衣荡秋千的妞"随处"可见
No, everyone has swings with girls in pajamas.
我的名片
My business card.
家庭清洁服务
Home cleaning service.
人家是开清洁公司的
She runs a cleaning company.
"苏菲的选择"
"Sophie's choice."
你知道这代表什么吗
You realize what this means?
我们侮辱了一名自食其力
We insulted a hard-working woman
还想帮我们达成梦想的善良女性
who was trying to help us attain our goal?
是的
Yes.
而且我也没得疱疹
And I don't have herpes!
我当初真该听你的话
I should have listened to you.
结识邻居是个大错误
Meeting neighbors is a big mistake.
结识邻居还说人家是妓女
And meeting neighbors and calling them a prostitute?
天大的错误
Bigger mistake.
而且还得自掏腰包付饭钱
Plus, we have to kick in 60 for the check.
我们该跟她说什么啊
What can we possibly say to her?
道歉 并请她尽情地放比吉斯的歌
That we're sorry, and please keep playing the Bee Gees
从早到晚 多大声都行
day or night as loud as she wants.
死到临头了你还傻笑
Not a good idea to be smiling right now.
我还在高兴我没得疱疹呢
I'm just so happy I don't have herpes.
你好 没打扰到你吧
Hi, is this a bad time?
有 打扰到正忙着花钱嫖我的
Yes. Yes, I'm in the middle of having sex for money
全布鲁克林男性恩客呢
with every man in Brooklyn.
你们俩坏坏妞来干嘛
What do you horrible, horrible girls want?
给 你落下了一部分"梦想"在餐厅
Here, you left part of your dream on the table.
我们还想来跟你道歉
And we want to apologize.
敦亲睦邻这种事 我还是第一次
I'm new at this whole being neighborly thing.
松软白妞有什么要说的吗
What does the fluffy one have to say?
谢谢你对我们如此大度
Thank you for being so generous,
还愿意给我们赚钱机会
and for offering to help us make more money
帮我们实现梦想
to accomplish our dream.
随便客套两句就能让我好过点吗
And this is supposed to make me feel better?
你们说我是妓女呢
You called me prostitute.
其实那也是在夸你啊
Actually, it's kind of a compliment
我们觉得男人会愿意付大把钞票
that we thought you were stunning enough
只为了跟你共赴巫山云雨
that men would pay to have sex with you.
这倒是真的
This is true.
进来吧
Come on in.
《周末夜狂热》是我最爱的电影
Saturday night fever is my favorite movie.
看看他啊 太性感了
Look at him. He's so sexy.
他不怎么样啊 还有点油腔滑调
He's not that cute, kind of oily.
你说得对
You're right.
她的确不适合当妓女
She would have made terrible prostitute.
这电视好棒啊
That's a nice TV.
是啊 全新的
Yeah, brand-new.
之前我还跟我的妞们
I have all my girls over the other night
办通宵观影派对呢
for viewing sleepover party.
这电视还是3D的呢
It's also 3-D.
那有送3D眼镜吗
Does it come with 3-D glasses?
有啊 就在那边的抽屉里
Yeah, in the drawer there.
-给 -麦克斯 这又不是3D电影
- Here. - Max, it's not a 3-D movie.
管它呢 这可是3D眼镜呢
Who cares? It's 3-D glasses.
来嘛 你不是说要从不同的角度看世界吗
Come on, you're always talking about wanting us to see things differently.
帅呆了
Oh, so cool.
这个秋千装得太妙了
This swing is a brilliant idea.
是为我未来别墅的阳台准备的
Yeah, it's for my porch at lake house.
何必等以后呢
But why wait?
梦想就在当下
Dream is now.